<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<HarryPotter>
	<item>
		<title>
			Sorcerer Awakening
		</title>
		<author>
			DevonBlack
		</author>
		<text>
			harry is visited by merlin&apos;s phoenix, due to merlin&apos;s last spell, which told harry about his powers. harry trains himself. IS HOGWRTS READY FOR HARRY&apos;S STORM?
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>
			EVERYTHING I EVER WANTED
		</title>
		<author>
			Liya249
		</author>
		<text>
			Everything was planned, the spring wedding, the house, the children. But not Tom. Tom was not part of the plan. Unplanned things happen after all.
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>
			Death is not the end
		</title>
		<author>
			SlytherinKing240699
		</author>
		<text>
			All is lost, Voldermort won. So why does Hermione Granger wake to find herself years before the events of the Second Wizarding War with all the memories of taking part in it. Time travel but not really.
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>
			Harry&apos;s girls part 1
		</title>
		<author>
			reviews
		</author>
		<text>
			Harry has met three girls on his new journey as a wizard and he will face challenges set by the headmaster to test if He is indeed the chosen one
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>
			I See Two
		</title>
		<author>
			An other pancakes
		</author>
		<text>
			One person can shift an entire story to a whole new direction. Avery is just the person for the job. Series rewrite with OC. Book 1
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>
			la bataille des quatre royaumes
		</title>
		<author>
			Enileme-R
		</author>
		<text>
			La dernière Ville du Royaume de Gryffondor s&apos;écroule sous le tyran du Royaume de Serpentard, gouverné par le terrible empereur Voldmort et ses sbires les Mange-Mort, Harry Potter le jeune prince et sa cousine Hermione sont forcés de fuir dans les bois pour aller chercher de l&apos;aide dans les royaumes voisins. Version 2.0
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>
			Second opposé
		</title>
		<author>
			reviews
		</author>
		<text>
			La guerre prend fin, mais à quel prix ? Pour Ron, il paye le plus élevé, dévastant Hermione. Comment se reconstruire sans les gens que l&apos;on aime ? A la fin de chaque guerre, vient le moment des enterrements, des adieux. Puis la douleur passe, et vient le moment de la joie, des mariages, des bébés, du renouveau.
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>
			Being Here
		</title>
		<author>
			reviews
		</author>
		<text>
			Harry is a Squib. Sure, he can attened Hogwarts thanks to Dumbledore but no-one wants him there. He&apos;s alone and he&apos;s angry and he doesn&apos;t know what to do until two strange men move in next door to number 4 Privet Drive. Written for IWSC Year 2 Round 1
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>
			Here We Go, Here We Go
		</title>
		<author>
			moonbird
		</author>
		<text>
			Bill and Molly butt heads over his choice of earring. Because what are families for? Written for IWSC Year Two WWN Issue One.
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>
			Second Chance, a new choice
		</title>
		<author>
			Maneeya
		</author>
		<text>
			Severus was dying in the shrieking shack, and he did indeed die. However, forces out of his control rendered him the ability to re-choose. going back and choose differently.
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>
			Une année d&apos;adulte
		</title>
		<author>
			reviews
		</author>
		<text>
			Recueil de drabbles divers. 1:12 sur la New Gen.
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>
			Allez tous vous faire F
		</title>
		<author>
			Freudentraene
		</author>
		<text>
			Harry en a marre. Complètement ras le chaudron. Il décide alors de mettre les points sur les I et de dire tout ce qu&apos;il a sur le cœur et... Il y en a des choses à dires.
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>
			Birds and Monsters
		</title>
		<author>
			serendipitymadness
		</author>
		<text>
			A slightly different purchase planning during his first visit to Diagon Alley means that Harry meets a completely different person than Draco Malfoy at Madam Malkins. How will this encounter change the fate of the world? And will two restless souls together be able to find some happiness and love in a ruthless world? HP/DG
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>
			Messages from No One
		</title>
		<author>
			Ailu Anidem
		</author>
		<text>
			When Hermione finds herself having a conversation with someone in a mysterious book that she bought, she soon finds herself immersed with the mysterious sender and makes it her mission to help them without realising just what she&apos;s gotten herself into.
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>
			Mundo Trouxa
		</title>
		<author>
			reviews
		</author>
		<text>
			Tradução de Mugglefied, de DragonGrin. &quot;Por crimes cometidos contra o mundo bruxo e trouxa enquanto menor de idade, por meio deste, condeno você a um ano sem magia&quot;. Draco ficou rígido, os joelhos travados para ajudar a mantê-lo em pé. Tantos espectadores. Potter e Granger estavam lá, sem o Weasley. Seus joelhos finalmente dobraram e ele caiu no chão, desmaiado&quot;. DRAMIONE.
		</text>
	</item>
</HarryPotter>
