<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><Twilight><item><title>Run to You</title><author>SehunsBae37</author><text>Bella has not been feeling complete with the absence of her best friend, and she can&apos;t bring herself to even act happy with her approaching wedding. She misses Jacob terribly but doesn&apos;t know what to do about it. However, Bella finally decides to listen to what her heart tells her and go after what it truly wants, and that means going after Jacob.</text></item><item><title>Orbiting Satellites – Book Three</title><author>Just4fun37</author><text>Story picks up 6 years after Breaking Dawn. Jake &amp; Nessie were captured by Joham who&apos;s trying create Vamp/Half-Vamp offspring w/Nessie. Once they&apos;re rescued Jake&apos;s near death &amp; Carlisle determines Nessie&apos;s pregnant. What will Jake, Nessie, &amp; the rest of the Cullens do? Read Orbiting Satellites – Book 1 &amp; 2 before this, to understand everything going on. JPOV &amp; RPOV All Canon</text></item><item><title>The Story of a Life</title><author>Seph Meadowes</author><text>What if, Izabella Swan was something no one had heard about before, that it was such a closely guarded secret.</text></item><item><title>Equinox</title><author>FairytaleBeginnings</author><text>Angela Weber was the pastor&apos;s daughter, the girl next door, and everybody&apos;s friend. She was not the object of romantic interest or the middle of a love triangle. Fate had other plans. [No Bella.]</text></item><item><title>Devil&apos;s Playground</title><author>Adrienne Cardoso</author><text>If you thought vampires and werewolves were the only supernatural creatures out there, think again. Emme Wildes comes from a long, distinguished line of witches. After her mother is banished, she elects to move in with her estranged aunts and fully commit to learning magic. Unfortunately for her, she has a lot to learn, and a coven of vampires certainly aren&apos;t making things easy.</text></item><item><title>The First Kiss</title><author>FarmerBill</author><text>Por causa de um questionário informações são descobertas. Talvez um primeiro beijo role em algum momento, mas antes as crianças vão ter que aprender uma ou duas lições. Todos humanos. É inspirada no livro &quot;O Primeiro Beijo&quot; de Marcia Kupstas.</text></item><item><title>Mine</title><author>reviews</author><text>Alexandra Faye has a lot to prove. Jacob Black has his hands full. Settle Down sequel. This is a very slow SLOWBURN!</text></item><item><title>The Most Perfect Storm</title><author>BlueJay8083</author><text>My take of Alice meeting Jasper on a cold, rainy day in Philadelphia in 1948. One-shot.</text></item><item><title>Desolation</title><author>Redana Crisp</author><text>At a young age, was left to fend for herself. After her best friend, her brother, leaving behind their sick mother. She&apos;s completely closed herself off. But after hundreds of decades ever, she stumbles upon someone she hasn&apos;t seen in a long time, her brother. Will she accept him back into her heart? Or is the damage too big for her to trust him again, and to love as well? Review!</text></item><item><title>LANDLINE: Segundas Oportunidades</title><author>mysteryheart</author><text>Bella sabe que su matrimonio está en problemas. Que lo ha estado por mucho tiempo. Una noche descubre una manera de comunicarse con el pasado e intenta arreglar su matrimonio antes de que siquiera comience. ¿Es eso lo que se supone que haga? ¿O Bella y Edward estarían mejor si nunca se hubiesen casado?</text></item><item><title>The Unforgivable</title><author>reviews</author><text>What really should have happened when jacob forced himself on Bella and Charlie pleaded indifference. Actions have consequences and i think. its time a couple of stubborn men learned that. Jacob-bashing. Not for jacob lovers ( currently experiencing technical difficulties with my chapters being cut off. please hold on while I try to fic the issue)</text></item><item><title>The unforgivable: Missing scenes</title><author>jovita.maciasruiz</author><text>here are the missing scene&apos;s from my story The unforgivable</text></item><item><title>seduciendo a un padre</title><author>Sami1997</author><text>Una chica obsesionada con un padre, primero es una aventura y luego se convierte en amor</text></item><item><title>Heartbeat</title><author>Clara370</author><text>Something is going on with Esme, she is crying, is warm, and can&apos;t hear as well</text></item><item><title>How To Say Goodbye</title><author>airedalegirl1</author><text>Sam and Emily have settled down and married. They are looking forward to a well earned happily ever after. Everything was perfect until tragedy struck. Will Emily survive or will Sam have to say goodbye to his reason for existing?</text></item></Twilight>